passionup.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy of PassionUp.com

**PASSIONUP PRIVACY POLICY  
LAST UPDATED: SEPTEMBER 21, 2009  
VERSION 1.0**

PassionUp.com Inc and its Subsidiaries are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") discloses how we collect and use information, and the choices that you can make about the way we collect and use your information.

If you are under 18, you should ask your parents or a guardian before you use our Services. If you are not yet 18, do not use our Service; do not download our products.

This Privacy Policy applies to any customers who use our Services. Collection, use, disclosure, and protection of personal information may be subject to different regulations outside the United States. Regardless, if you use our Sites, Products or Services you agree to abide by this policy.

Sites Covered by This Policy: www.PassionUp.com and other sites we own that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively “Sites”). This Privacy Policy also applies to our Toolbar (collectively “Products”). This Privacy Policy may also apply to new Sites and Products we develop.

**_Overview of Our Policy_**  
PassionUp.com Poetry E-Greeting Website (We refer to our software and Products throughout this agreement as our “Services”).  
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices regarding: 

  * Information We Collect
  * How We Use Your Information
  * How We Use and Share Your Information
  * Your Choices
  * The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

By accessing Sites, using our Services, providing information requested or by continuing to use our Services, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Sites or our Services.

We may make available shorter versions of this Privacy Policy. We also may supplement this policy for specific Services. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our summary or supplement, this policy will govern. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy. By accessing the sites or using the Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy as modified.

**_Some Terms We Use in This Policy_**  
_Offers_ include e-mail, promotions, advertisements contests and third-party software presented by our Partners and us.

_Personally Identifiable Information (PII)_ is any information that identifies or could be used to identify, contact or locate you. It also includes your credit card number.

_Partner_ is an advertiser, or other entity with whom we have a business relationship to provide Offers.

_Service_ Poetry eGreeting Site

_Subsidiary_ is an entity wholly owned or related to PassionUp.com Inc

_User_ means an individual that has accessed the Sites on which we host our Products or Services.  
_We and Our_ refer to PassionUp.com Inc and its subsidiaries.

_You and Your_ refer to each user and his or her agents.

**_Personal Information We Collect_**  
We may collect personal information at various times when you use our Services. Your participation is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information that we request by choosing not to participate in an offer or exiting our Sites and Services.

 _Installation_

. During the installation process, we will present you with Offers. You may choose not to accept our Offers. 

_Contacts/IP Information_

. If you voluntarily submit information or contact us (e.g. password request, technical support), we may keep a record of this communication. We do not merge this information with your Personally Identifiable Information.

**_Aggregate Information We Collect_**  
When you use our Services, we may collect tracking information such as your IP address, browser type, the type of operating system you use, details about your computer hardware, the applications you have installed on your PC, the domain name of your Internet service provider, and pages you visited on our Sites. None of the information identifies you personally and we do not link aggregate information to Personally Identifiable Information.

 _Cookies_

. A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser. Cookies are stored on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. We and our Partners use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once you close your browser, the cookie will terminate. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s help file.

We use cookies to: 1) Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers). We also use cookies to store your zip code and other information you have submitted for other services, such as displaying your local weather; 2) Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing our Services is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, usage by registered users and unregistered users, and to help target advertisements based on user interests; 3) Allow our Partners to track visits to their sites and stores. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called "clickstream" or "click trail" and may also describe which pages you have seen; 4) Measure certain traffic patterns, for example which of our Sites you have visited. We use this information to understand our users' habits so that we can make each new experience on a Site a better one. We may also use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you will see. We do not store Personally Identifiable Information in our cookies and we do not tie the information in our cookies to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

Some of the Partner Offers on our Services may also use cookies. We have no control over our partners’ privacy policies. We also have no control over their cookies, the information collected and its use.

 _Web Beacons or Pixels_

. We and our Partners employ a software technology that helps us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web beacons or Pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. They track your online Web movement. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, we embed Pixels invisibly on Web pages. They are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixels to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

Some of the Partner Offers may also use Pixels. We have no control over our partners’ Pixels. We also have no control over how they use information collected.

 _Global Unique Identifiers_

. A GUID (global unique identifier) is a randomly generated alphanumeric identifier used to indicate a unique installation of our Products or Services. We may create a GUID when you install our Products or Services. We use GUIDs to track installations and to enable features and functionality for specific customers who subscribe to our Products and Services. We do not tie the information gathered by GUIDs to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

 _Software Information_

. We employ a technology that allows us to determine the operating systems you are using and to view your computer’s registry. Software installed on your computer has unique registry keys. By viewing your registry, we are able to detect whether you have a compatible operating system, compatible versions of DirectX, and Flash Player installed. We use your registry information to determine whether our software offers are compatible with software already present on your PC. We do not tie registry information gathered to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

 _Hardware Information_

. Your computer’s operating system also stores hardware information that we examine to determine your computer’s hardware configuration including the amount of memory and the type of video card your computer has, as well as the speed of your processor. We use the information to determine whether our software offers are compatible with your computer hardware. We do not tie hardware information to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

**_How We Use Your Information_**  
Our primary goal is to make our Services more useful to you. By knowing about you, we are able to deliver relevant Services and Offers. We maintain a secure database of all Information collected on our Sites and Services.

 _Research_

. We study users' demographics and interests using your information. We also use cookies, pixels, software information and server log files to better understand and serve you. We compile and analyze this information on an aggregated basis. We may also share this aggregated data with current and potential Partners.

 _Third Parties and Advertising_

. Third parties advertise on our Sites, and we also contract with third parties to serve ads across the Internet. These third parties may serve ads about our products or services, or third party products or services in which, based on your Session Data, we or our business partners believe you may be interested. These third parties may seek to use cookies and pixel tags, including those collected on our Site, to track Session Data about the ads you have seen and types of things in which you appear interested. These third parties may also use combined information about your visits to our Site and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that may be of interest to you. You can opt-out of the third party advertising program by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>. Opting out of a network does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns.  
When you click on a third party advertisers' link from our Site, you will be taken off of our Site and will enter the third party's site. We are not responsible for such third party's sites. You should carefully review the privacy statements of any other site you visit, because those privacy statements will apply to your visit to that site, and may be very different from our policy.

**_Sharing Your Personal Information with Partners._**  
The following describes some of the ways that we may disclose your information to our Partners:

 _Search Partners_

. We may transmit your search queries (made on the Site or within one of our Software Offers) to search Partners, who use this information to provide us with search results, which we then will display to you.

 _Third-Party Advertisements and Software_

. When you request or submit your information online to a Partner in response to any Offer, we may transfer your information for each request made to that Partner. If we transfer your Personally Identifiable Information, such information becomes subject to the Partners’ privacy policy.

 _Our Products_

. We do not require you to provide Personally Identifiable Information during the installation process. However, when you use any of our Partners’ Software Offers you may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information. 

_Other Limited Circumstances_

. From time to time, we may validate the information in our database by employing a validation service. In those instances, we will disclose your information pursuant to confidentiality agreements. In addition, we disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, 45% of our users are female) when we market to current and prospective Partners and for other lawful purposes.

 _Legal Disclosure_

: We may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our policies or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights, property, users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain service, and improve our Products and Services.

 _Sale, Merger or Asset Transfer_

. We may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that we or all of our assets are acquired, customer information, including any information collected through the Sites or the Services would be one of the transferred assets.

**_Your Choices_**

 _Cookies_

. By modifying your browser preferences, you can choose to, accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or you can reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, you may be unable to use our Services.

 _Offers_

. We may from time to time, send you e-mail regarding third party promotions, as well as other, Products and Services. In addition, we may occasionally send you e-mail or direct postal mail about other products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive e-mail or postal mail from us, you can tell us by e-mailing us here. You can also write to Attn: Customer Care, PassionUp.com Inc, PO Box 61431, Honolulu, HI 96839. Be sure to include your full name and address, along with the information you submitted during your initial registration including postal address and e-mail, and tell us that you no longer wish to receive offers from us. You also have the option of unsubscribing from e-mail Offers by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every e-mail offer from us.

 _Additional Information_

. At any time you may send us an e-mail here or by postal mail addressed to PassionUp.com Inc Attention: Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues, PO Box 61431, Honolulu, HI 96839to request a listing of all personal information disclosed by us to third parties or Partners. If requested, we will provide an e-mail response within thirty (30) days informing you of the recipients of your Personally Identifiable Information and the information disclosed to third parties. 

**_Security and Passwords_**  
We cannot and do not ensure or warrant the security of any information collected, transmitted over the Internet, or maintained in your user profile. You agree that any data transmission you make or receive through the Site or the Service is at your own risk.

Account information for our members is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. Do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password. Also, remember to sign out of your account and close your browser when you have finished your visit. This ensures that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.  
No method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and therefore we cannot warrant or guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.

**_Children's Online Privacy Protection Act_**  
We do not knowingly collect information about children. Should a child make known to us his or her Personally Identifiable Information, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her Personally Identifiable Information. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit. The Federal Trade Commission ("FTC") regulates the means by which web site operators collect and use personal information from children under 13, pursuant to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (the "Act"). For more information about the Act and children's on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC's web site at www.ftc.gov/privacy. For safety tips on privacy visit www.OnGuardOnline.gov.

**_Miscellaneous Provisions_**

 _Disclaimer of Liability_

. YOUR USE OF OUR SERVICES IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. OUR SERVICES (INCLUDING ALL CONTENT AND FUNCTIONS MADE AVAILABLE ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH OUR SITES) IS PROVIDED "AS IS." WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER ABOUT: (1) THE ACCURACY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT; (2) THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SERVICES AVAILABLE, INCLUDING THAT IT IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER COMPONENTS THAT MAY INFECT, HARM, OR CAUSE DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR ANY OTHER PROPERTY WHEN YOU ACCESS, BROWSE, DOWNLOAD FROM, OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.  
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO OUR NEGLIGENCE, SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR SPECIAL DAMAGES RELATED TO (A) THE USE OF, (B) THE INABILITY TO USE, OR (C) ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE CONTENTS AND FUNCTIONS OF OUR SITES AND SERVICES, EVEN IF WE OR OUR REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN NO EVENT SHALL OUR TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT OR TORT, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) EXCEED $1.00.

 _Indemnification_

. You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold us and all of our agents, directors, employees, information providers, licensors and licensees, officers, and subsidiaries (collectively, "Indemnified Parties") harmless from and against any and all liability and costs (including, without limitation, attorneys' fees and costs) incurred by you in connection with any claim arising out of any breach by you of this Privacy Policy. You will cooperate as fully as reasonably required in our defense of any claim. We reserve the right, at our own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you and you shall not in any event settle any matter without our written consent.

 _International Policy_

. Our Services are hosted by servers in the United States. Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, we will transfer the personal information you provide to us to the United States. By submitting your personal information, you fully understand and consent, to its transfer, storage and processing in the United States.

 _Enforcement/Redress_

. If you feel that we have not followed our Privacy policy, please let us know. Also, if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy policy, its implementation, or would like a written copy, please feel free to contact us at:

PassionUp.com Inc  
Attention: Customer Care – Privacy Policy Issues  
PO Box 61431  
Honolulu, HI 96839

Alternatively, if you would like, contact us via e-mail here
